Maybe zoom in out a bit.
So your book, Choosing Courage.
What's the central thesis here?
The central thesis, I guess going back to where we
started is really that courage is a personal choice and it's
a responsibility.
And it helps to think not about courage as if it's some,
sort of, property. You know,
I often say if you do an autopsy of somebody,
you won't find some stock of courage somewhere in the body.
There is no such thing.
So it helps to think about courageous action.
And once you say it's about whether you do something in
those critical moments, you then can assume personal
responsibility.
And in a sense, the thesis is that we don't allow
ourselves to say that any other virtue is just the responsibility
of some,
or that we should do it some of the time.
You know, if you think about fairness or moderation
or kindness,
so many other principles are cardinal virtues.
Those aren't just the responsibility of one of my
10 co-workers or myself,
1/10 opportunities,
right?
I'm not really an honest person, Jim,
you know that.
I leave that to the other guy.
My boss is honest.
That's good enough for the team.
Why have we allowed that?
Right.
We wouldn't say that about any of these other traits.
So these virtues.
So why do we allow that in the realm of courage?
Frankly, I think we let ourselves off the hook too frequently.
And part of it's because we're afraid,
and so the book talks a lot about how to address fears.
And part of it's because we're not very skilled,
and so we see so many screw ups in ourselves and others
when people do try to behave courageously that we conclude,
you know, it's just too dangerous.
And so the book is fundamentally about saying,
hey, you got to choose your moments,
but then you have to be willing to take on some risk and you have to
be willing to do the work to increase your competency.